When your mind is a mystery.  You can survive the
wilderness. But can you escape your past?
Wrecked is a mystery, thriller, horror film directed by Michael Greenspan.
A man awakens in a car wreck at the bottom of a steep cliff.
He can't remember who he is or how he got there, but a report over the radio fills in some of the blanks, as it
describes a violent bank robbery and names a perpetrator who happens to be sitting dead in the back seat.
Man, played by Adrien Brody.
Woman, played by Caroline Dhavernas.
George Weaver, played by Ryan Robbins.
Man in the Woods, played by Adrian Holmes.
Raymond Plazzy, played by Adrian G. Griffiths.
Eric Stapleton, played by Lloyd Adams.
Wrecked is a 2010 Canadian thriller film, directed by Michael Greenspan, written by
Christopher Dodd, produced by Kyle Mann and starring Adrien Brody.
It was released by IFC Midnight Films on April 1, 2011.
The film explores themes of amnesia, robbery, hallucination, forest, alone.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.